Becker, Frank J.; Papers apap224
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Correspondence, 1953-1964; 2; 2.4 cubic ft.
  - Immigration, F, 1955-1960 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Immigration, F, 1956-1957 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Immigration, F, 1961 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Immigration, F, 1962 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Immigration, F, 1963-1964 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Immigration G, 1953-1954 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Immigration G, 1954-1957 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Immigration G, 1955-1956 (Box 2 (2-Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - Immigration, G, 1958 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Immigration, G, 1959-1960 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Immigration, G, 1961 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Immigration, G, 1962 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Immigration, G, 1963 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Immigration, H, 1954 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Immigration, H, 1954-1958 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Immigration, H, 1955-1956 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Immigration, H, 1959-1960 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Immigration, H, 1960-1961 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Immigration, H, 1961-1962 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Immigration, H, 1963-1964 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Immigration, I, 1953 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Immigration, I, 1955-1956 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Immigration, I, 1957-1958 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Immigration, I, 1959-1960 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Immigration, I, 1960-1962 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Immigration, I, 1963-1964 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Immigration, J, 1955-1956 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Immigration, J, 1957-1958 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Immigration, J, 1960 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Immigration, J, 1961-1964 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Immigration, J, 1963-1964 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Immigration, K, 1953-1954 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Immigration, K, 1955-1956 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Immigration, K, 1955-1957 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Immigration, K, 1958 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Immigration, K, 1959-1960 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Immigration, K, 1960-1962 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Immigration, K, 1963-1964 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Immigration, L, 1953 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - Immigration, L, 1955-1956 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Immigration, L, 1957-1958 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Immigration, L, 1959-1962 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Immigration,L, 1963-1964 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 35)
  - Immigration, Lan, Hom Tew, Wong Kwong, Svey, Wong, 1958-1960 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 36)
  - Immigration, M, 1953-1954 (Box 3 (2-Correspondence), Folder 37)
  - Immigration, M, 1955-1956 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Immigration, M, 1957-1958 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Immigration, M, 1958-1959 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Immigration, M, 1959-1960 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Immigration, M, 1961 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Immigration, M, 1961-1962 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Immigration, M, 1963-1964 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Immigration, Mc, 1955 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Immigration, Mc, 1958 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Immigration, Mc, 1960 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Immigration, Mc, 1964 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Immigration, N, 1953 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Immigration, N, 1954-1955 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Immigration, N, 1956-1958 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Immigration, N, 1961-1962 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Immigration, N, 1963-1964 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Immigration, Naturalization (Congratulatory Letters), 1961 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Immigration, Naturalization (Congratulatory Letters), 1962 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Immigration, Naturalization - Citizens, 1963-1964 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Immigration, O, 1953-1954 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Immigration, O, 1955-1958 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Immigration, O, 1957-1958 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Immigration, O, 1960 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Immigration, O, 1961-1962 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Immigration, O, 1963-1964 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Immigration, P, 1952-1955 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Immigration, P, 1956 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Immigration, P, 1957 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Immigration, P, 1958 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Immigration, P, 1959 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - Immigration, P, 1960 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Immigration, P, 1961 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Immigration, P, 1962 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Immigration, P, 1963-1964 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Immigration, Q, 1962 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Immigration, Q, 1962-1963 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Immigration, R, 1953-1954 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Immigration, R, 1955-1956 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Immigration, R, 1956-1958 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Immigration, R, 1959-1960 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Immigration, R, 1960-1962 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Immigration, R, 1962-1964 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Immigration, Riccio, Raffaele, 1958-1960 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Immigration, S, 1953-1954 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Immigration, S, 1955-1956 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Immigration,S, 1957 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Immigration,S, 1958 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Immigration,S, 1959 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Immigration, S, 1960 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Immigration, S, 1961 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Immigration, S, 1962 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Immigration, S, 1963-1964 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Immigration, T, 1953-1954 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Immigration, T, 1955-1956 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Immigration, T, 1957-1958 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Immigration, T, 1959-1960 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Immigration, T, 1961 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Immigration, T, 1962 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Immigration, T, 1963-1964 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Immigration, V, 1953-1954 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Immigration, V, 1955-1956 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Immigration, V, 1957-1958 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Immigration, V, 1959-1960 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Immigration, V, 1961-1962 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Immigration, V, 1963-1964 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Immigration, W, 1953-1954 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Immigration, W, 1955-1956 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Immigration, W, 1957-1958 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Immigration, W, 1959-1960 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Immigration, W, 1961-1962 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Immigration, W, 1962-1964 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Immigration, Y, 1955 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Immigration, Y, 1957-1958 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Immigration, Y, 1961 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Immigration, Y, 1964 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Immigration, Z, 1953-1954 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Immigration, Z, 1954-1956 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Immigration, Z, 1957 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Immigration, Z, 1958-1960 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - Immigration, Z, 1962 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Immigration, Z, 1962-1963 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Servicemen, A, 1953-1954 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Servicemen, A, 1955-1956 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 35)
  - Servicemen, A, 1958 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 36)
  - Servicemen, A, 1959 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 37)
  - Servicemen, A, 1959-1960 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 38)
  - Servicemen, A, 1961-1962 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence), Folder 39)
  - Servicemen, A, 1963-1964 (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Servicemen, B, 1953-1954 (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, B, 1955-1956 (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Servicemen, B, 1957-1958 (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, B, 1960 (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, B, 1961-1962 (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, B, 1963-1964 (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, Bejarano, Luis, 1960-1962 (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Servicemen, C, 1952-1954 (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Servicemen, C, 1955-1956 (Box 7 (2-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Servicemen, C, 1957 (Box 8 (2-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Servicemen, C, 1957-1958 (Box 8 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, C, 1959 (Box 8 (2-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Servicemen, C, 1960 (Box 8 (2-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Servicemen, C, 1961 (Box 8 (2-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Servicemen, C, 1961-1962 (Box 8 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, C, 1963-1964 (Box 8 (2-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Servicemen, Caputo, John J., 1951-1956 (Box 8 (2-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Servicemen, Crownfield, Eleanor, 1959-1962 (Box 8 (2-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Servicemen, D, 1953-1954 (Box 8 (2-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Servicemen, D, 1955 (Box 8 (2-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Servicemen, D, 1957-1958 (Box 8 (2-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Servicemen, D, 1959-1960 (Box 8 (2-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Servicemen, D, 1960 (Box 8 (2-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Servicemen, D, 1961 (Box 8 (2-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Servicemen, D, 1962 (Box 8 (2-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Servicemen, D, 1963-1964 (Box 8 (2-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Servicemen, Dragstedt, Carl, 1958 (Box 8 (2-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Servicemen, E, 1952-1953 (Box 8 (2-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Servicemen, E, 1954-1956 (Box 8 (2-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Servicemen, E, 1957-1958 (Box 9 (2-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Servicemen, E, 1959 (Box 9 (2-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Servicemen, E, 1960 (Box 9 (2-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Servicemen, E, 1961 (Box 9 (2-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Servicemen, E, 1961-1962 (Box 9 (2-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Servicemen, E, 1963 (Box 9 (2-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Servicemen, F, 1953-1954 (Box 9 (2-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Servicemen, F, 1956 (Box 9 (2-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Servicemen, F, 1957-1958 (Box 9 (2-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Servicemen, F, 1960 (Box 9 (2-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Servicemen, F, 1960-1961 (Box 9 (2-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Servicemen, F, 1962 (Box 9 (2-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Servicemen, F, 1963-1964 (Box 9 (2-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Servicemen, Farrell, Stanley, 1962-1963 (Box 9 (2-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Servicemen, G, 1954 (Box 9 (2-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Servicemen, G, 1955-1956 (Box 9 (2-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Servicemen, G, 1957-1958 (Box 9 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, G, 1958-1959 (Box 9 (2-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Servicemen, G, 1960 (Box 9 (2-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Servicemen, G, 1961 (Box 9 (2-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Servicemen, G, 1961-1962 (Box 9 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, G, 1963-1964 (Box 9 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, H, 1953-1954 (Box 10 (2-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Servicemen, H, 1955 (Box 10 (2-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Servicemen, H, 1957-1958 (Box 10 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, H, 1959 (Box 10 (2-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Servicemen, H, 1960 (Box 10 (2-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Servicemen, H, 1961 (Box 10 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, H, 1961-1962 (Box 10 (2-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Servicemen, H, 1962-1964 (Box 10 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, Huber, Erwin W., 1960-1961 (Box 10 (2-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Servicemen, I, 1953-1954 (Box 10 (2-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Servicemen, I, 1959 (Box 10 (2-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Servicemen, I, 1961 (Box 10 (2-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Servicemen, J, 1953 (Box 10 (2-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Servicemen, J, 1954-1955 (Box 10 (2-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Servicemen, J, 1957-1958 (Box 10 (2-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Servicemen, J, 1959-1960 (Box 10 (2-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Servicemen, J, 1961-1962 (Box 10 (2-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Servicemen, J, 1963 (Box 10 (2-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Servicemen, K, 1953-1954 (Box 10 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, K, 1955-1956 (Box 10 (2-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Servicemen, K, 1957-1958 (Box 10 (2-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Servicemen, K, 1959-1960 (Box 10 (2-Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Servicemen, K, 1960-1961 (Box 10 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, K, 1960-1962 (Box 10 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, K, 1962-1964 (Box 10 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, L, 1953-1954 (Box 11 (2-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Servicemen, L, 1955-1956 (Box 11 (2-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Servicemen, L, 1957-1958 (Box 11 (2-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Servicemen, L, 1959-1960 (Box 11 (2-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Servicemen, L, 1961 (Box 11 (2-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Servicemen, L, 1962 (Box 11 (2-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Servicemen, L, 1963-1964 (Box 11 (2-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Servicemen, Lavale, Ronald, 1956-1958 (Box 11 (2-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Servicemen, M, 1952-1954 (Box 11 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, M, 1955-1956 (Box 11 (2-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Servicemen, M, 1957-1958 (Box 11 (2-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Servicemen, M, 1958-1959 (Box 11 (2-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Servicemen, M, 1960 (Box 11 (2-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Servicemen, M, 1960-1961 (Box 11 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, M, 1962 (Box 11 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, M, 1963-1964 (Box 11 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, Mc, 1957-1958 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Servicemen, Mc, 1959-1960 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Servicemen, Mc, 1960-1961 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Servicemen, Mc, 1961-1962 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Servicemen, Mc, 1963-1964 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Servicemen, N, 1953-1954 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Servicemen, N, 1956-1958 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Servicemen, N, 1960 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Servicemen, N, 1961-1962 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Servicemen, N, 1962-1964 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Servicemen, Navey, Edwin, 1958 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Servicemen, Nystrom, J, 1962 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Servicemen, O, 1953-1954 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Servicemen, O, 1955-1956 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Servicemen, O, 1957-1958 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Servicemen, O, 1960 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Servicemen, O, 1961-1962 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Servicemen, O, 1962-1963 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Servicemen, P, 1953-1954 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Servicemen, P, 1954-1956 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Servicemen, P, 1957-1958 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Servicemen, P, 1958-1959 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Servicemen, P, 1960 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Servicemen, P, 1960-1961 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Servicemen, P, 1961-1962 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Servicemen, P, 1963-1964 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Servicemen, Pappas, James, 1960-1963 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Servicemen, Pilkington, Marines, 1964 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Servicemen, Q, 1956-1957 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Servicemen, Q, 1957 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Servicemen, R, 1952-1954 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - Servicemen, R, 1955-1956 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Servicemen, R, 1956-1958 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Servicemen, R, 1958-1959 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Servicemen, R, 1959-1960 (Box 12 (2-Correspondence), Folder 35)
  - Servicemen, R, 1960-1961 (Box 13 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, R, 1961-1962 (Box 13 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, R, 1963-1964 (Box 13 (2-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Servicemen, S, 1953-1954 (Box 13 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, S, 1955-1956 (Box 13 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, S, 1957-1958 (Box 13 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, S, 1959 (Box 13 (2-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Servicemen, S, 1959-1960 (Box 13 (2-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Servicemen, S, 1960 (Box 13 (2-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Servicemen, S, 1961 (Box 13 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, S, 1961-1962 (Box 13 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, S, 1963-1964 (Box 13 (2-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Servicemen, S, 1963-1964 (Box 14 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, Simons, Robert P., 1957-1958 (Box 14 (2-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Servicemen, Simons, Marshall, 1951-1954 (Box 14 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, Sternberg, Alan - [RESTRICTED], 1955-1958; 1960-1962 (Box 14 (2-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Servicemen, T, 1953-1954 (Box 14 (2-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Servicemen, T, 1955-1956 (Box 14 (2-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Servicemen, T, 1957-1958 (Box 14 (2-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Servicemen, T, 1958-1960 (Box 14 (2-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Servicemen, T, 1960-1961 (Box 14 (2-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Servicemen, T, 1961-1962 (Box 14 (2-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Servicemen, T, 1963-1964 (Box 14 (2-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Servicemen, Trop, Albert L., 1955-1956 (Box 14 (2-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Servicemen, U, 1954 (Box 14 (2-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Servicemen, 1958 (Box 14 (2-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Servicemen, U, 1959 (Box 14 (2-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Servicemen, U, 1960-1961 (Box 14 (2-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Servicemen, U, 1963 (Box 14 (2-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Servicemen, V, 1953-1954 (Box 14 (2-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Servicemen, V, 1955-1956 (Box 14 (2-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Servicemen, V, 1957-1958 (Box 14 (2-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Servicemen, V, 1959-1960 (Box 14 (2-Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Servicemen, V, 1961-1962 (Box 14 (2-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Servicemen, V, 1963-1964 (Box 14 (2-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Servicemen, W, 1953-1954 (Box 14 (2-Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Servicemen, W, 1955-1957 (Box 14 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, W, 1957-1958 (Box 14 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, W, 1959-1960 (Box 14 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Servicemen, W, 1961 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Servicemen, W, 1962 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Servicemen, W, 1963 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Servicemen, Weston, Doctor George M., 1955; 1957 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Servicemen, Woltin, Carl, 1958-1959 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Servicemen, Y, 1958 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Servicemen, Y, 1959 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Servicemen, Y, 1962 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Servicemen, Z, 1952-1953 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Servicemen, Z, 1955 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Servicemen, Z, 1958 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Servicemen, Z, 1959-1960 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Servicemen, Z, 1961-1962 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Servicemen, Z, 1964 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Veterans, A, 1955-1956 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Veterans, A, 1960 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Veterans, A, 1961-1962 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Veterans, A, 1963 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Veterans, Avidon, Samuel, 1953-1954 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Veterans, B, 1955-1956 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Veterans, B, 1956-1958 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Veterans, B, 1959-1960 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Veterans, B, 1961-1962 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Veterans, B, 1963-1964 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Veterans, Bartels, Robert, 1954 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Veterans, Bates, Richard Paul, 1951-1953 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Veterans, Buchan, Herbert J, 1954 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Veterans, Budischak, Steve G., 1953-1954 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Veterans, C, 1955-1956 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Veterans, C, 1957-1958 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Veterans, C, 1958-1959 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - Veterans, C, 1959-1960 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Veterans, C, 1961 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Veterans, C, 1962 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Veterans, C, 1964 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 35)
  - Veterans, Cain, Nelson A., 1953 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 36)
  - Veterans, Clement, Emil, 1953-1954 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 37)
  - Veterans, Columbine, Henry F., 1954 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 38)
  - Veterans, Columbine, Robert L., 1953 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 39)
  - Veterans, Comentino, Frank L., 1958-1959 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 40)
  - Veterans, Cromwell, Herbert J., 1953 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 41)
  - Veterans, D, 1954 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 42)
  - Veterans, D, 1955-1956 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 43)
  - Veterans, D, 1957 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 44)
  - Veterans, D, 1959 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 45)
  - Veterans, D, 1961-1962 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 46)
  - Veterans, D, 1963 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 47)
  - Veterans, Dorf, Alfred L., 1958-1959 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 48)
  - Veterans, E, 1954 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 49)
  - Veterans, E, 1956 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 50)
  - Veterans, E, 1957 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 51)
  - Veterans, E, 1961-1962 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 52)
  - Veterans, E, 1963 (Box 15 (2-Correspondence), Folder 53)
  - Veterans, Eberach, John F., 1958-1962 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 0)
  - Veterans, F, 1954 (Box 16 (2-Correspondence), Folder 3)